Class of 1923 Records, 1919-1983
Smith College Archives
Class of 1923 Records
1919-1983
Smith College. Class of 1923.
RG 80 UUID:126f7589-f51d-4ba4-af70-44e4e54272e0
17 boxes (14.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1923.
Historical Note
The Class of 1923 was the forty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1923 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1923, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1923 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Campus Catechism n.d. (Box 1955, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 4)
- Freshman Frolic 1919 (Box 1955, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind 1919 (Box 1955, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1919-1920 (Box 1955, Folder 7)
- Groups 1919-1923 (Box 1955, Folder 8)
- History 1919-1923 (Box 1955, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 11)
- Last Chapel 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 12)
- Class Letters 1954-1976 (Box 1955, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1924 (Box 1955, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1926 (Box 1955, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1955, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1955, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 1955, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1943 (Box 1955, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1955, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 1955, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 1955, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1973-1978 (Box 1955, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1983-1988 (Box 1955, Folder 24)
- Secretary's Book 1921-1983 (Box 1955, Folder 25)
- Senior Dramatics 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 2)
- Songs n.d. (Box 1956, Folder 3)
- Sophomore-Senior Banquet 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 4)
- Songs 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)